#### Contact

+923164272026 (Mobile) masoodusman2@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/usman-masood-ab2167185 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

.NET Core Microsoft Dynamics 365 REST API

#### Languages

Urdu (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Functional Consultant Associate

Certified ASP.NET MVC Developer

# **Usman Masood**

.NET Core | Microsoft Dynamics 365 | Power Platform & CE Consultant at Systems Limited

Lahore District

## Summary

An Information system professional who blends diversified experience with an extensive background in CRM Consultancy especially in CRM dynamics, ASP.NET Core, SQL Server.

Governing an experience of 3+ years in CRM & Banking Industry. Having a previous conduct of successful multi million dollar CRM & banking implementations for a great number of clients. Also exceptional at dealing with the sales and service industry. A multi-capacitated team member capable of articulating complex technical concepts, guiding new associates and developing effective relationships with clients.

**Business Domains:** 

Human Recourse Management Systems
Medical Domain
Customer Service
Banking Sector
Sales

Specialties:

ASP.NET MVC

Microsoft Dynamics 365

**Entity framework** 

SQL Server

Rest API's

**jQuery** 

Power Platform

Bootstrap

Angular

Experience

Systems Limited
Microsoft Dynamics CRM Consultant
June 2021 - Present (9 months)
Pakistan

AutoSoft Dynamics (Pvt.) Limited
.NET Core Developer
February 2020 - June 2021 (1 year 5 months)
Lahore District, Punjab, Pakistan

I have Worked on Human Resource Management System. Worked on PMC (Performance Measurement Life Cycle) modules the for Banking Systems. I have also worked on training module where participants can take online trainings, can give online tests and get certificate against the training. Worked on ESS (Employee Self Service Portal) where employee can manage their Information, Qualification, Relatives details, Attendance, Apply leaves and many other things.

NTM Soft ASP.NET MVC Developer January 2019 - February 2020 (1 year 2 months) Lahore, Pakistan

Worked as Web Developer in NTM Soft (Pvt.) Limited. I have worked in C#, ASP.NET MVC, Rest APIs, MSSQL, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap during this time Period. I have worked on different projects. Mostly I have worked as a backend developer.

Worked on school ERP system which includes complete financial system, student reports and fee collection reports. My responsibilities in this project is to develop Student Admission Module and Fee Management Module.

## Education

COMSATS Institute of Information and Technology Bachelor's degree, BSCS · (2016 - 2020)